[
	{
		"question": "What is a balance between theory and observation?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.9949300289154053,
			"start": 126,
			"end": 133,
			"answer": "Science"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What did the Greeks start answering mythology questions with?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.9910808205604553,
			"start": 356,
			"end": 363,
			"answer": "science"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "Who criticized \u201chistoricism\u201d and \u201cholism",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.9697088003158569,
			"start": 1537,
			"end": 1543,
			"answer": "Popper"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the argument against historicism and holism?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.9226347804069519,
			"start": 45,
			"end": 71,
			"answer": "Science is not predictable"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "Who was the father of many contemporary scientific disciplines: Chemistry Biology Physics",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.9185206890106201,
			"start": 1230,
			"end": 1240,
			"answer": "David Hume"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "Who did Turing start his paper with an observation about human \u201ccomputers\u201d?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.9103566408157349,
			"start": 235,
			"end": 246,
			"answer": "Alan Turing"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What is one example of unfalsifiable theories?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.691037654876709,
			"start": 1240,
			"end": 1282,
			"answer": "Freud\u2019s psychoanalysis Conspiracy theories"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What is a condition that has to be met for something to be the case if a human gets blown into bits then they will die green = sufficient condition, blue = necessary condition",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.5602138638496399,
			"start": 1113,
			"end": 1134,
			"answer": "A necessary condition"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What was Alan Turing's paper that tried to provide a solution to these problems?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.5544392466545105,
			"start": 230,
			"end": 234,
			"answer": "1936"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What does the term \"science\" differ in meaning Danish - videnskab English Refer to only \"natural sciences\" or \"hard sciences\" Does not refer to what?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.5235480666160583,
			"start": 178,
			"end": 188,
			"answer": "humanities"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the most nuanced view on empiricism Science consists of?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.47976112365722656,
			"start": 251,
			"end": 266,
			"answer": "problem solving"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What do we move towards semantics when we are interested in what expressions refer to?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.4153687655925751,
			"start": 84,
			"end": 103,
			"answer": "what they are about"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "Who approached the study of science from the angle of its history?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.2849486172199249,
			"start": 1119,
			"end": 1191,
			"answer": "Thomas Kuhn and the scientific revolutions In a stark contrast to Popper"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What means that for any sentence it can be proved whether the sentence or its negation is in the theory?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.2754538357257843,
			"start": 0,
			"end": 12,
			"answer": "Completeness"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What did Mathematicians want to be the explanation of the fundamentals of mathematics on logic specifically on the notion of a \u201cset\u201d?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.24537938833236694,
			"start": 560,
			"end": 564,
			"answer": "set\u201d"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "How can scientists test the coherence of the theory?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.1493711769580841,
			"start": 509,
			"end": 528,
			"answer": "Step 2 - scientists"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What does science predict the future states of planets but not the future state of physics?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.09089089184999466,
			"start": 140,
			"end": 147,
			"answer": "Physics"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "How does the barber shave himself?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.0800655335187912,
			"start": 1126,
			"end": 1156,
			"answer": "he does not shave those people"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.06898380815982819,
			"start": 1147,
			"end": 1199,
			"answer": "it gives us a lot of new information about the world"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the most visible example of gender bias in science Political feminism?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.05207991227507591,
			"start": 783,
			"end": 815,
			"answer": "women were very underrepresented"
		}
	}
]
